another thing because
do you expect to enter Paradise without
undergoing the same test
as those before you
they suffered hardships and adversity
and was so sick enough that the
messenger and
um
they suffer with hardship and adversity
and was so safe enough that the
messenger of those who believed were
himself
the word is God's Victory indeed God's
Victory is always
so
the idea here is to
worship God Alone no matter what happens
but all circumstances it's a matter of
knowledge
that God is one and he's the only Master
he's the only one that benefits of God
he's the only one who controls the mind
the hearts of the people around you
the American love you or help you or
care about you or don't care
and with this knowledge it doesn't
matter what happens
adversity or happiness
it's a fix
definite knowledge
and you know that it doesn't matter what
happens so
also we are here
for the test
and God wants to be proud of you and
want to show you off to the angels and
say look at my servants
he or she worships me no matter what
happens
without ever seeing and this is the
whole idea of our existence
and the end of the verse says indeed
God's Victory is always near
it must be anointed also here that after
the test
there is a final test
after the final test that is absolutely
there's nothing but think simple enough
as God promises when you come to the
conclusion that you worship God Alone
and it takes a long time the road is
long and hard
it's a continuous struggle
but there will come a time when you are
perfect worshiper of God Alone
then there is no hardship
and you would can see this in Surah 24
these are some of the verses that you
must remember all the time page 243
the Red Cross
because God promises those respect to
Christ
2.3
God promises those among you who believe
and work righteousness that they will
make their kings on Earth as he did for
those before them and that he will
establish for them they are religion
foreign
izing anything besides me
if anyone just believes after this that
these are the women
come and sit next to that
next tomorrow
see this this promise is true now do you
remember Joe
had lots of parts of adversity
but uh
once he passed the test
he recovered his heads recovered he
recovered his payment and even twice as
much
he recovered his work and twice as much
so he was under the test for as long as
he needed to be tested he to prove
himself and the same is true with that
also you must think of the adversity as
a cleansing and policy process
when you join the awareness of God I
don't want to expect some problem at the
beginning
because you're cleansing all the masked
sins all the past errors
and this can be cleansed only by praying
for them in this world
so all the adversity that you have at
the beginning to come to come join this
mosque you will have five or ten years
of adversity
across the topology process
polishing you know how polishing goes
detect a piece of Rock
they put it in polishing machine very
noisy
shipping off pieces
but then what comes out is a beautiful
gym
and that's what what will come out after
you go through the policy process
polishing is not too easy
so what I'm telling you is that there is
a final test
verse 3 and 4.
the verse is a tour of time
another day
it's 401.
verse two let's put first two at the end
of it
says whoever observes righteousness
towards God he would create an exit for
him
an exit of every problem
and provide for him when he never
expects
When You observe God
the sacrifice a result or
a source of income
strictly for the sake of God he would
provide for you what you never expect
for the best of the day
401.
the end of verse 2.
this is the verse I wanted to remember
whoever observes righteousness towards
God he will create an exit for him and
provide for him once we never expect
anyone who trusts in God God will
surprise him
God always carries out his decisions
you have come to the conclusion that God
is the king the absolute ruler of the
little girls
and you'll carry out these promises and
this decision
you just you just have to believe it you
must have absolute confidence in it
tomorrow there is a mandatory law
insurance law
we have
quite a few of us have decided that we
have insurance for God but if you are
with God you have the best insurance
and you just have to believe that
nothing would happen to you what
happened to the rest of God this this is
the difference between the insurance
companies and God's insurance
we don't have anything happen to you
your caught your head
with the with the insurance companies
will have the accidents and the
insurance company will pay for you
you have the agony of the insurance of
the accident
and the inconvenience of losing the car
from you
or having an operation
and the companies will pay
but you just have to have the confidence
that when you have insurance with God
nothing will happen to you
also you must know that if God wants to
get you he'll get you whether you have
insurance or not
that says they cannot escape from me
that's what you said deserve the pills
or a little accident
for Earth and sickness
you can't get away from your insurance
company yeah
when you have to then you have to we
will not
buy insurance unless we have to but but
it appears that God is already taking
care of us
because the law enforcement to put the
prosecutors are all protesting the law
and they are making an official
enforce it
so I called the civil liberties Union
myself and I told them this country
that's our religious beliefs everything
and they didn't do anything about it
so we will not buy insurance until we
have to
because the Quran says if you have to
eat pork or drink wine or do anything if
you have to without being malicious of
the liver
when you're not committing the sin
but what I'm saying is What God Says and
provide for you who else you never
expect you must you must know that
you must have that confidence
if you have the slightest doubt it will
not work
and this insurance business we we're in
a
to finance for a long time
we had that conviction to the extent I
told you about our friend tariff when
the guy says
those are the insurance
well and he said I have a choice of God
so what's his phone number
he didn't he just it wasn't taken I mean
it was the natural question of coming
afterwards but then of course
because he had a person in his hand on
the paper he was there so write the
phone number
it was a tune-up place
somebody
so uh
got all those cursed out his desists
he's the absolute
he runs this country
or any government anywhere
if you go to the end of verse 4
says whoever observes righteousness
towards God God will make everything
easy for him
everything will go easy for you
you will not suffer any party
there's absolutely no humidation for the
Servants of God
you go apply for a job and you will be
the boss because your soul takes over
the place
and you see them
running to serve you
they may not be Elijah
she'll see it
whoever observes righteousness towards
God God will make everything easy for
him
this is God's promise as documented here
in this planet
so we'll go back now to page 23.
about hardship as a mandatory test
over and over we see people who are
immensely Wealthy on the TV and they're
complaining about unhappiness how
unhappy they are
foreign
earthquakes
hurricanes floods all these are
punishments
punishments and tests
because all these things are absolutely
controlled by God
there is a statement that will answer
your question
Surah I believe 64. let's look at this
beautiful
64 plus or minus two sure so I'm gonna
find it for you
yeah 11 verse 11 11.
there's no disasters so it's accepted
accordance with God's will
[Music]
this is this is the law
no disaster strikes except in accordance
with God's will
no no pain no disaster nothing happens
except by personal decree from God
because it is not simple
it's not it's not easy to
so that's a painful headache for example
it has to be a personal degree from God
outside
your question Diana yeah
well God is angry let's go every drop of
water is made everything in this world
is miserable
every piece of ice that fellow Denver
who gave a miserable time
was measured yeah
yeah everything is planned
every the minutest detail is very
carefully planned alhamdulillah
nothing is coincidental or haphazard
love it
as individuals as Nations as a world
just think every drop of water is
measured exactly where it goes
where it's going to fall how many inches
from an ant that's crawling motion
ground that's right
okay
recipients of charity
they ask you about Charities say
Charities shall go to the parents the
relatives the orphans the poor and the
aliens any righteous work you do God is
fully aware thereof
fighting may be forced upon you though
you dislike it
but you may dislike something which is
actually good for you and you may like
something which is actually bad for you
God knows why you do not know
they ask you about the desecration of
the Sacred months by fighting therein
say fighting during the sacred months is
sacrilege
but repelling the people from the path
of God and disbelieving in him and in
the sacredness of the Sacred mosque and
evicting the people there from are all
worse sacrileges in the sight of God
oppression is worse than murder
they will continue to fight you until
they revert you from your religion if
they could
those who revert from religion and die
as disbelievers have wasted their Works
in this life and in the Hereafter they
have deserved hell wherein they abide
forever
as for those who believe immigrate and
strive in the cause of God they have
deserved God's mercy God Is Forgiven
merciful
so it's two different subjects here
the 215 talks about the charity
and it tells us specifically that
the charity first goes to those that are
closest to us that those were most
responsible for our parents and our
relatives
and then next to those that
that really need economic help or don't
have someone else to rely on the oracles
and the poor and then the alien
and so this is a carefully uh
we're given the details of how charity
should be distributed
first of the parents if they need it
they don't need it
so you know in other words each takes
care of his own
and the H1 takes care of his own there
will be no misery in the world
the relatives are rich
then you find orphans
children children will have no parents
one or two killers oh God and then any
pork you put and then
this one
see any righteous works with you God is
fully aware of it and it seems that
charity is more than just economic
health it can do any kind of help
any
righteousness
doing what is right in this world toward
other people here for simply politeness
or
anything we try to do to make the
the world better
treat the other people as we'd like
for merciful towards you
people around us
then God is
is because
we want to express God's mercy
we want uh
we desire God's forgiveness and God's
mercy and these qualities
in by showing our appreciation the
desired form we express
[Music]
the next subject
is on fighting
which I take to mean
basically in a war type of situation
though it may be
well when we think about him we think of
taking up Arms Of Violence rather than
simply arguments so at another level it
could be
simply not giving in to it
to uh any kind of
oppressions which may be
economically political or social but
no I you know
the only there's only one reason in
Quran for fighting
and has to do with the freedom to
worship God Alone
that's it
there's absolutely no other reason
for fighting I wonder if it's gonna
interfere with your freedom of
practicing the worship of God
I know personally trying to impose any
new religious
or to prevent you from practicing your
religion
there is the only reason for fighting
the fighting may be imposed upon you
that somebody come to say hey don't pray
you cannot pray the issue Allah cannot
pray
but if your country gets into war with
another country and you're required to
go and fight
you might get drafted or anything
yeah
not believe in God
like the pressure comes to embed this
country for the purpose of turning
everybody into an atheists
that's the cause of God the only
fighting is
they're unforeseeable reasons or
circumstance
but fighting for land is because of
burdens right because of country
it's all the
rest of life because that did not create
this bottle
I think we have Jesus and passport
everything you're forced to defend
yourself when somebody else wants to
drive you away from your your own life
you have to fight also
or do you just you know run away to suck
your friends
it isn't because of God
I mean if they the what it says about
evicting you from your houses or you'll
hit them from where they addicted you
and you know
if they're simply fighting up
they're not perceiving religious reasons
they're probably perceiving yeah
differences
did we did we go through the rules of
warrior because
all right did we go through that
connection yeah yeah we did yeah
that Wars are only Justified
almost the defensive yeah
in Japan but those rules about they say
do not fight them in the sacred mosque
unless they attack you there
a question here worshiping God I don't
have somebody come to say you can't you
can't practice this
so you know this is really cool so we
have to fight there
you'll be surprised Anything Can Happen
yeah
we just happened to have a format of an
argument around this building anyway as
you know
and he's
he's one rare person who comes before he
he was leery of the Hadith so he came to
see us just because we believe in the
Quran alone but anyway what I want to
tell you is that people try to defense
the sign I think
the other side
so there are invisible forces around us
here you don't need to do anything this
Edge
is the edge of metal
mental debate
rather than
swords and fighting
anyway you can't fight because of that
Orlando Florida
unless you're attacked anyway
foreign
if it's part of the institution that's
involved
you don't earn your living setting
liquor for example
I suppose you went to work I was asking
about joining the Armed Forces or to
join the armed forces and there's no war
this was like any job
let's suppose your government gets into
war with another country that's when you
have to make a decision whether this is
because of God or not
all right
I suppose uh you're working for a big
company and they're producing something
that you know like
or say nepalm or chemical weather
you know maybe you're not directly
involved in the manufacturing are you
protesters there's no wall perfectly all
right because
prepare the maximum power that you have
the war itself aggression is
so joining the Armed Forces or making
weapons or
anything that is not war
I'll look at this wall then you have to
make a decision if it isn't the cause of
God alone so it's okay to have a nuclear
around the race that's right
but
if we didn't have uh nuclear weapons of
this country it can be used
to protect us
again
the effective weapons the bombs
Commandments one of his Commandments is
prepare the maximum power in capacity
when I see it
um
yeah I I meant to talk to you about this
once before because you said trust in
God and don't make any weapons
pretty empty strike which is attacking
first
they call it pre-empty strikes
it's a matter of strategy
Surah 9 verse 41.
he's a very demobilized
Surah 8 verse 16.
to the Commandment to your child
124.
60 you shall prepare for them all the
force and the equipment you can master
in order to deter the enemies of God and
your enemies as well as others you are
not aware of
why God knows them
anything you have spent in the course of
that would be irritated to you without
believing Justice
it's a very respectful commandment to
prepare to prepare
you must you must always have a
deterring
for okay
so it is you trust in God but you follow
what he says
that's right that there was an early
battle on the list of the Muslims are a
great round numbers
and we looked at it from the Strategic
point of view the logistic point of view
the the numbers of each soil and they
tried to analyze it militarily and this
doesn't make sense the Muslims defeated
to this believer
also the Battle of your mooc when we did
and we will do something the level of
numbers
the money
okay
oppression is worse than murder
okay it's an attempt to manipulate
somebody's mind
and
to
make other people follow one's own
material desires
whoever did depresses
it's not just that
they're trying to change your mind
but to make you revert
to a situation of unbelief in other
words the Muslims now have come
they vary for the truth all right
and for you to go from truth back to
unbelief that is what ourselves
murder of his own so it's not a matter
of just changing your belief but it's
going back to unbelief which is terrible
and Quran says many times once you have
to believe many people will try to
is that you revert to Andrew so that is
a
it's terrible because the the punishment
for
the punishment for unbelief after belief
is greater than just Anthony from
beginning to end
I think Quran says that to a few times
it says it in the next week
from the religion and lies disbelievers
have wasted their Works in this life
they have deserved hell and they were
there forever
and those who believe
immigrate we strive in the cause of God
so it's telling I think that if we are
oppressed then we can't fight him it's
better to get up and leave and go
someplace
we can
follow where they guys
Commandments
to write I guess it's telling us to
fight if we can if not to try to get
away from that situation
foreign
because people have pointed out many
times I think they
interpret this verse out of context how
can operation of persecution divorce the
remark that they say but not many if you
read the whole thing
I think what it means is this in the
long run going to hell
if this was the reminder nothing
offensive I think this is what it means
if you die some people don't seem to
care at this um oppression uh
but I don't understand why the enemies
we have to take this in conjunction with
the other verses and tell us about dying
I mean we're here in America
this country is fanatic about the
business
foreign
[Music]
it was because
foreign
just
play uh
even the people here in this country
from over there
and the Quran
it might be violent because affecting
their dog and their either and actually
it doesn't imply now that I'm saying
okay
immigration means you go to the spot
where you worship God Alone really
without the secure
immigration
foreign
but you you are all believers in God
alone
in the Quran alone but you cannot say
this overseas
in the so-called Muslim countries
that you will have any influence
doing this they would actually put them
trial and repeat it
that's a question
did you say a moment ago that the tax
course is
foreign
thank you
um
I think so
something else
any questions on the
foreign
which is actually good for you you go
apply for a job you're watching from God
alone and you don't get the job
why
because it's not good for you
that's why you got to apply for jobs and
you you don't care it's going to get it
or not because you know that God will
give you the job that's good for you
you submit to God you submit to that
nation of Nations he knows what
circumstances you would exist under
every job you're applying for
so what you do when you're applying for
a job is you knock on all the goals and
God will open the one that is good for
you
so when you don't get a job it is not
something it's something you dislike it
that you might dislike something which
is actually good for you it's good for
you that you didn't take that job
okay
so you can think of a million things
that you may like which is best for you
and you may like something which is
disgusting
that's an important question is that you
are taking advantage of the fact that
you involve the ambition
he knows exactly what is best for you
the toxic and some gambling prohibited
and some benefits for the people however
their evil outweighs their benefits they
ask you of what to give as Charity say
the excess God does clarify generation
for you that you may replace
upon this life and the hereafter
they ask you about the orphans say the
best thing is to bring them up as
writing individuals
if you mix their property with yours you
shall treat them as members of your
family
God is fully aware
and who the righteous are
at that will
he could have decreased hardship rules
God is Almighty why
but
first there is a commander in verse 219
and it's straightforward
commandment God is probably
us to have instructions and to to do
gambling
and God says there is a hero in this
having intoxicants or doing
gambling
the life is a perfect night for this bar
yeah because the people around them were
emboding
directly
but it's not that I'm sorry while you
are studying God's message which is one
of you gets a hundred times for a while
tonight
people are out there breaking God's law
with intoxicants and you laugh at this
hour
yesterday
he says he says the tickets
foreign
money from these things
for example
selling wine or you know that make
profit that brings profit too
this is a good point the Quran is
accurate
and the Quran cannot the Quran
acknowledges the fact that some people
Farmers plants right and sell them and
the lots of people have jobs because of
why
the benefit
therefore if we follow that law we have
to eliminate
I don't deny that this is one of the
reasons that it will give up employment
benefits to hundreds of people not us as
a brother uh heir of the same you can
also
means
something else open and about
for example I noticed that
in certain cases
when some people are feeling bad and so
on they give them a shot
you have to put your love is very
important it will help them temporarily
but Indonesian it's bad if it becomes a
habit I think this is a possibility to
talk about
a small point it's giving its own
quality and so this is